centralbank.net 2010-12-23

# Central Bank - Privacy Statement

## Privacy Policy

As required by law, we are providing to you our Privacy Policy. We will provide notice of our Privacy Policy annually as long as you maintain an ongoing relationship with us.

## Our Promise 

As a valued customer, Central Bancompany affiliates are committed to providing you with exceptional service and product offers. We are also committed to the belief that maintaining the confidentiality of our customer's information is at the core of our relationship with our customers. Our Board of Directors has adopted this Privacy Policy so that you will understand what information we collect and how we use it. 

## Information We Collect 

We collect and retain personally identifiable information about you when we believe that the information will assist us in providing products, services and other opportunities to you and in managing your accounts and services. One of the main reasons we collect certain information is to protect your account and to identify you. The information we collect will be used to comply with certain laws and regulations that may apply to us and to help us understand your financial needs as we design or improve our products and services. We will also use your information to administer your account and transactions and to provide you with products and services that will best assist you. We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:

  * Information we receive from you on an application or other form
  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others
  * Information we receive from a credit bureau

**Examples of nonpublic personal information include information regarding your account balance, credit card use, and payment history.**

## Information We Disclose 

We understand that you expect the personal information you have entrusted to us will be handled with great care. We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers or former customers to anyone, except as permitted by law. Please be assured that we will NEVER provide medical information that we may obtain in insurance applications to any affiliate or to any associate without a need to know. 

## Central Bancompany Affiliates 

We are permitted by law to share information about our experiences or transactions involving you or your account with us with companies related to us by common ownership or control (“affiliates”). We may also share other information about you or your account (such as information we receive from you in applications and information from credit bureaus) with our affiliates. Our affiliates provide important services and products designed to provide you with the highest quality financial services. If you prefer that we not share information with our affiliates that does not relate solely to our affiliates’ experiences or transactions with you or your account (such as application information and credit bureau information), you may direct us not to share this information by completing the return card and mailing. You cannot “opt-out” on behalf of any other customer. 

We may share information about you within our family of companies so we can serve you more efficiently, offer you products and services that we know would benefit you and make it easier to do business with us. However, you may limit our affiliates, such as trust, credit card or insurance, from marketing their products or services to you. This limitation would be based on your credit or transaction information that we have previously collected from you and share this information with them. This information includes your income, your account balances, and your payment history. This limitation does not apply in certain circumstances, such as if you currently do business with one of these affiliates. If you prefer that these affiliates limit the marketing of their products or services, you may direct us not to share this information by printing the opt-out form (located in the right-hand column under the heading "Related Links") completiing, and mailing it to the address stated on the form. You cannot “opt-out” on behalf of any other customer.   

## Third Parties 

We work with select outside companies to develop special offers for you, which many of our customers find valuable. **We do not sell or share customer information to unrelated third parties for the third parties to use for their own purposes.** We do share information with companies that print checks for us, mail customer statements or letters, or provide data processing services. These companies are acting on our behalf when they provide these services and are obligated to maintain the information they receive in a confidential manner. They are never authorized to use the information for any other purposes.

For example, we also provide information:

  * When you authorize us to release information
  * To credit reporting agencies
  * To other parties when it is necessary or helpful in processing transactions at your request, including other financial institutions and networks involved in processing your transactions
  * In connection with maintaining or servicing your account with us or with another entity as part of a private label credit card program
  * To comply with a law, regulation, court order, or subpoena
  * To verify the existence of your account and general information about the condition of your account for a merchant or other financial institution
  * To local, state, and federal authorities if we believe a crime may have been committed involving your account
  * To our independent auditors, consultants, or attorneys and to agencies that regulate us

We may disclose all of the information we collect as described above to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements. Of course, those third parties would contractually agree not to use the information for any other purpose. If you close your account(s) with us, we will continue to follow this Privacy Policy.

## Our Security Procedures

One of the ways we protect your information is by limiting access to information about you to those associates with a reason to know your information in order to provide products or services to you. In addition, we train our associates about the importance of maintaining the confidentiality of customer's information. We take appropriate disciplinary action to enforce our associate's privacy responsibilities. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your nonpublic personal information.

## Links to Other Site 

Our policy discloses the privacy practices for Central Bancompany and Affiliate Bank websites. But we also provide links to other websites. When you leave Central Bancompany Affiliate Bank website you will be going to sites that are beyond our control. We try to ensure that links that leave our site are clearly labeled. Other sites may send their own cookies, collect data, or solicit personal information. The privacy policies and procedures described here for Central Bancompany and its affiliate banks do not apply to any external links. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of any site you link to from ours, especially if you share any personal information. Be informed. You are the person best qualified to protect your own privacy.

## Our Family 

  * Boone County National Bank
  * Central Bank
  * Central Bank of Lake of the Ozarks
  * Central Mortgage Company
  * Central Trust & Investment Company
  * City Bank
  * Dogwood Insurance Agency, LLC
  * Empire Bank
  * First Central Bank
  * First National Bank of Audrain County
  * First National Bank of St. Louis
  * InvestorServices Insurance, Inc
  * Jefferson Bank of Missouri
  * Metcalf Bank
  * ONB Bank and Trust Company
  * Ozark Mountain Bank
  * Third National Bank
